{
    "subject": "resource/Sarah_Silverman",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Steve_Martin",
    "human_readable": "Sarah Silverman was influenced by Steve Martin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.973565936088562,
            "question": "Did Steve Martin have a significant impact on Sarah Silverman's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9667224884033203,
            "question": "What impact did Steve Martin have on Sarah Silverman's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9372324347496033,
            "question": "Who was an influence on Sarah Silverman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8708480000495911,
            "question": "Which comedian influenced Sarah Silverman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8468586206436157,
            "question": "Name a comedian who inspired Sarah Silverman."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7881110310554504,
            "question": "What comedians did Sarah Silverman cite as influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7435697913169861,
            "question": "What comedic figures influenced Sarah Silverman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.688075602054596,
            "question": "Which comedian is considered a source of inspiration for Sarah Silverman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.53644859790802,
            "question": "Whose style of comedy did Sarah Silverman draw inspiration from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36226409673690796,
            "question": "Who was a role model for Sarah Silverman in comedy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sarah Silverman was influenced by Steve Martin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7568_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Whose style of comedy did Sarah Silverman draw inspiration from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7568_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which comedian is considered a source of inspiration for Sarah Silverman?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7568_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What comedic figures influenced Sarah Silverman?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7568_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7568_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention several instances where Steve Martin is mentioned as an influence or inspiration for Sarah Silverman. In document 17.txt, it's stated that Sarah Silverman fell in love with Steve Martin when she was 14 and even wrote \"I love Steve Martin\" on her bedroom ceiling. Additionally, in document 45.txt, it's mentioned that Sarah Silverman is a devotee of Steve Martin in her New Hampshire childhood."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances indicating that Sarah Silverman was influenced by Steve Martin. Specifically, the document `17.txt` mentions that she wrote \"I love Steve Martin\" on her bedroom ceiling when she was 14 years old, and the document `68.txt` and `111.txt` mention several well-known figures (including Tina Fey and Carl Reiner) describing Steve Martin as an inspiration or genius to Silverman."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}